

Erdem Doğanay

Jr. Web Developer

I worked as an intern at Digitaktek for 3 months. The company used php, jquery, javascript, html, css as programming languages. I was editing the company's websites for corporate companies. Currently, I have been working in hepapi technology for 1 year. I am making web site arrangements and development with .NET core .

BIOGRAPHY

Birth Date: 24.03.1987

Birth Place: Kazan/Turkey

Nationality: Turkey

PERSONAL INFO

.NET: Expert

Php: Expert

HTML: Experienced

CSS: Talented

.NET: 1 have been .NET

Php: 1 have been PHP

HTML: 1 have been HTML

CSS: 1 have been CSS

KEY SKILLS

Phone: 0534474980

Mail: erdemdgny@gmail.cim

Web: www.erdem.con

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com

CONTACT

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022

Jr. Web Developer

Digitatek, Turkey

I have supported many

corporate web solutions of the company

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022

Jr. Web Developer

Hepapi Technology, United Kingdom

I have supported many corporate web solutions of the company

EXPERIENCE

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022

Ankara University Computer Programming Turkey

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022

Anadolu University Management Information System Turkey

13.03.2022 - 13.03.2022

Hacettepe Üniversitesi Ankara Bahrain

EDUCATIONS

English: A1 (Beginner/Elementary)

Spanish: A1 (Beginner/Elementary)

Turkish: C2 (Proficient)

 $L\,A\,N\,G\,U\,A\,G\,E\,S$